http://www.sensorex.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentPrivacy PolicyHome/Privacy Policy Privacy PolicyChris Walker2020-01-27T14:45:33-08:00Sensorex Privacy PolicyOur Commitment to PrivacyWe respect your privacy. In the interest of transparency, this notice explains our online information practices. We want to enable you to make informed choices about how your information is collected and used.In this Privacy Policy, “we”, “us” and “our” means Sensorex, Inc. We own and run the websites with the domain names www.sensorex.com, www.ph1phmeter.com, www.phelectrode.com, and www.smartaquameter.com.If you have any questions or concerns about our website, online data or privacy policy management and implementation, please contact us, using the Message Subject “Comment About Website.”Information CollectedVisitors may browse our websites without revealing their identity or providing details about the reason for their interest.When some types of additional information are requested via our website, we may ask you to provide us with some basic details that include your name, organization’s name, your location, your professional email address and optionally, your professional telephone number. We may also ask you to provide us with information about your industry or the way you use water quality monitoring products. These details are used to respond to requests quickly and with the best available information and resources.In the majority of cases, we provide educational resources and information without requesting any personal details.The Way We Use Collected InformationWhen users agree to provide us with personal information we will generally use this in one of four ways as outlined below:Details requested when downloading or otherwise obtaining enhanced informationEnhanced information includes resources such as application webinars, case studies, and some pricing.  In many cases, Sensorex requests a professional email address in order to deliver requested resources and respond to specific questions. Sensorex may store email addresses in a secure contact database in order to provide users with additional relevant resources and content. Users have the option to opt out of receiving email from Sensorex at any time (see “Unsubscribing” below).If any user feels that their privacy is being violated through the use of their email address, please do not hesitate to contact us and we will take action to resolve the issue.Users registering to receive Sensorex newslettersUsers who register to receive news and promotions or blog post notifications from Sensorex will be emailed with electronic copies of this content or a link to its location on the internet. To enable us to do this the details of those users will be collected and stored in a secure emailing list database.UnsubscribingUsers wishing to “unsubscribe” from receiving future mailings will be given the opportunity to do so in every mailing. Users may also opt of mailings in a certain category, while remaining subscribed to mailings of other categories. Users that unsubscribed will not receive automated emails but may be contacted directly by a member or our sales or customer service team.Users requesting a response through completion of a “Contact Us” form Questions or comments submitted through our contact form will be answered as soon as possible by our in-house team, usually within 1-2 business days.Our Use of CookiesA “cookie” is a small information file which if accepted on to their computer by a user will enable a website to recognize them if they return to that website. When users opt to give their details in relation to an enhanced information request, Sensorex may provide a cookie that removes the need for the user to enter those details or go through the detail request screens a second time. If a user does not accept the cookie or subsequently deletes it then no functionality will be lost but the same details will be requested the next time that user wishes to obtain enhanced information.These pieces of information are used to improve services for you, for example:enabling a service to recognize your device so you don’t have to give the same information more than oncestoring usernames and passwords for conveniencemeasuring the performance of our website to help us understand how you use our services and how we can improve themproviding you with personalized services, both through our website and through other mediaOur use of third party CookiesWe use Google Analytics and HubSpot software to help us improve the usability of our website and provide you with personalized services and information.For further details on the cookies set by Google Analytics, see the link below.Cookies set by Google AnalyticsFor further details on the cookies set by HubSpot, see the link below.Cookies set by HubSpotHow to opt out of cookiesOur website works better with cookies enabled, and we advise you to keep cookies enabled. However, you can choose to reject cookies. You can use your browser to delete and reject cookies.Our Policy On Sharing Collected InformationSensorex will not loan, rent or sell the information you provide us with to any party outside Sensorex without obtaining your permission. Within Sensorex, information held may be used by authorized employees located both within and outside the United States, though in all locations the above privacy policy is valid.Accessing and Updating of Collected InformationYou are entitled to see the information held about you and you may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. If you wish to do this, please contact us with the Message Subject “Comment About Website.”GDPRFor detailed information on Sensorex’s privacy policy as it relates to the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), visit our GDPR Data Protection Policy page. If you would like to examine, modify, or delete your data, you will find a form to notify us on this page.Email SensorexFind a DistributorTechnical SupportPrivacyGDPR Data Protection PolicyOther PoliciesRESOURCES Specifications & InstructionsWhite PapersSDS DownloadspH CalculatorManufacturer Cross-Reference GuidesSENSOREX, Inc.11751 Markon DriveGarden Grove, CA 92841 USA +1 (714) 895-4344 +49 (0) 34327 91164 +91 93 87 064044 +420 389 603 703
Expect longer lead times due to delays resulting from COVID-19. Dismiss
